Architecture Slide Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- France (Box 5)
  - Cities (Box 5)
    - Maillezais (Box 6)
    - Marmoutier (Box 6)
    - Mossaic (Box 6)
      - S. Pierre Mossaic (Box 6)
        - Exterior (Box 6)
        - Exterior Sculpture (Box 6)
          - Various (Box 6)
          - Tympanum (Box 6)
          - Left wall (Box 6)
          - Right wall (Box 6)
          - Trumeau (Box 6)
        - Interior (Box 6)
        - Cloister [Slide boxes 33-34] (Box 6)
    - Montceaux-L'Etoile Church [Slide box 34] (Box 6)
    - Montmajor (Box 6)
    - Murbach (Box 6)
    - Neuvy (Box 6)
    - Nevers (Box 6)
      - S. Etienne (Box 6)
        - Exterior (Box 6)
        - Interior (Box 6)
    - Nivelles (Box 6)
    - Nogent-Sur-Oise (Box 6)
    - Norroy-Sur-Vair (Box 6)
    - Orcival (Box 6)
    - Orleans (Box 6)
    - Ottomarsheim (Box 6)
    - Paray-Le-Monial (Box 6)
      - S. Pierre (Box 6)
        - Plans & Sections (Box 6)
        - Exterior (Box 6)
        - Interior (Box 6)
    - Paris (Box 6)
    - Parthenay (Box 6)
    - Perigoeux (Box 6)
      - S. Frond (Box 6)
    - Perreccy les Foyes [Slide box 35] (Box 6)
    - Poitiers (Box 6)
    - Pompierre (Box 6)
    - Rousillon (Box 6)
    - Rucqueville (Box 6)
    - S. Benoit Sur Loire (Box 6)
      - Abbey Church (Box 6)
        - Exterior (Box 6)
        - Interior (Box 6)
        - Capitals (Box 6)
    - St. Gilles Du Gard-Arles (Box 6)
      - Exterior (Box 6)
      - Exterior Sculpture (Box 6)
    - St. Guilhem Le Desert (Box 6)
    - S. Loup-de-Naud (Box 6)
    - St. Martin of Boscherville [Slide box 36] (Box 6)
    - S. Martin De Canigou (Box 6)
    - S. Michel-De-Cuxa (Box 6)
    - St. Savin (Box 6)
    - St. Vincent Des Pres (Box 6)
    - S. Wandrille (Box 6)
    - Saulieu (Box 6)
    - Semur en Brionnais (Box 6)
    - Souillac (Box 6)
    - Souvigny (Box 6)
    - Thiers (Box 6)
    - Toulouse (Box 6)
      - Cathedral of S. Etienne (Box 6)
      - S. Sernin [Slide boxes 36-37] (Box 6)
    - Tournus [Slide box 37] (Box 7)
      - S. Philibert (Box 7)
        - Plans & Sections (Box 7)
        - Exterior (Box 7)
        - Interior (Box 7)
    - Tours (Box 7)
    - Uchizy (Box 7)
    - Uzes (Box 7)
    - Vezelay (Box 7)
      - La Madeline (Box 7)
        - Plans & Sections (Box 7)
        - Exterior (Box 7)
          - Various (Box 7)
          - West Façade (Exterior Sculpture) (Box 7)
        - Narthex (Box 7)
          - Central Portal [Slide box 37-38] (Box 7)
          - Tympanum & details [Slide box 38] (Box 7)
          - Left & Right Portals (Box 7)
        - Interior (Box 7)
        - Capitals (Box 7)
    - Vienne (Box 7)
    - Vignori (Box 7)
- Germany (Box 7)
  - Cologne [Slide box 38-39] (Box 7)
  - Essen [Slide box 39] (Box 7)
  - Essen-Werden (Box 7)
  - Hersfeld (Box 7)
  - Hildesheim (Box 7)
    - Cathedral (Box 7)
    - S. Michael (Box 7)
      - Exterior (Box 7)
      - Interior (Box 7)
      - Details (Box 7)
    - Hirsau (Box 7)
    - Koenigs-lutter (Box 7)
    - Komburg (Box 7)
    - Laach (Box 7)
      - Maria Laach (Box 7)
    - Limbourg an der Haardt [Slide box 40] (Box 7)
    - Mainz (Box 7)
      - Cathedral (SS. Martin & Stephen) (Box 7)
    - Mettlach (Box 7)
    - Munstereifel (Box 7)
    - Quedlinburg (Box 7)
    - Regensburg (Box 7)
    - Speyer (Box 7)
      - Exterior (Box 7)
      - Interior (Box 7)
    - Trier (Box 7)
    - Untergreisslau [Slide box 41] (Box 7)
    - Werden (Box 7)
    - Worms (Box 7)
      - Cathedral (Box 7)
      - Synagogue (Box 7)
    - Wurzburg (Box 7)
- Italy (Box 7)
  - General (Box 7)
  - Acqui (Box 7)
  - Agliate (Box 7)
  - Albe (Box 7)
  - Alife (Box 7)
  - Almennos S. Bartolomeo (Box 7)
  - Amalfi (Box 7)
  - Ancona (Box 7)
  - Arezzo (Box 7)
  - Aquila (Box 7)
  - Arsago Seprio (Box 7)
  - Assisi (Box 7)
  - Bari (Box 7)
  - Bitonto (Box 7)
    - Cathedral (Box 7)
  - Bologna (Box 7)
  - Borgo San Donnino (Box 7)
  - Canosa (Box 7)
  - Capua (Box 7)
    - Triumph Gate of Frederick II (Box 7)
  - Caserta Vecchia (Box 7)
  - Cassino (Box 7)
  - Castelvetrano (Box 7)
  - Cefalu [Slide box 42] (Box 7)
  - Civate (Box 7)
  - Como (Box 7)
    - S. Abondio (Box 7)
  - Empoli (Box 7)
  - Fabriano (Box 7)
  - Ferrentillo (Box 7)
  - Ferrara (Box 7)
    - Cathedral (Box 7)
  - Fidenza (Box 7)
  - Fiesole (Box 7)
    - Badia (Box 7)
  - Florence (Box 7)
    - Baptistry (Box 7)
      - Exterior (Box 7)
      - Interior (Box 7)
    - S. Minato al Monte (Box 7)
      - Exterior [Slide boxes 42-43] (Box 7)
      - Interior [Slide box 43] (Box 8)
      - Choir & Pulpit (Box 8)
      - Pavement (Box 8)
      - Tabernacle (Box 8)
    - S. Reparata (Box 8)
  - Genoa (Box 8)
  - Lodi Vecchio (Box 8)
  - Lomello (Box 8)
  - Lucca (Box 8)
    - Churches (Box 8)
      - Cathedral (Box 8)
      - S. Michele (Box 8)
  - Mantua (Box 8)
  - Milan (Box 8)
    - Churches (Box 8)
      - S. Ambrogio (Box 8)
        - Exterior [Slide boxes 43-44] (Box 8)
        - Interior [Slide box 44] (Box 8)
      - S. Nazaro (Box 8)
  - Modena (Box 8)
    - Cathedral (Box 8)
      - Exterior (Box 8)
      - Interior (Box 8)
      - Sculptural details (Box 8)
  - Monreale, Palermo (Box 8)
    - Cathedral (Box 8)
      - Exterior (Box 8)
      - Interior (Box 8)
      - Cloister [Slide boxes 44-45] (Box 8)
  - Monte Cassino [Slide box 45] (Box 8)
  - Monte Sant'Angelo (Box 8)
  - Monza (Box 8)
  - Murano (Box 8)
    - S. Maria e Donato (Box 8)
  - Noli (Box 8)
  - Orvieto (Box 8)
  - Ostia (Box 8)
  - Palermo (Box 8)
    - La Cuba (Box 8)
    - Cubola (Box 8)
    - Martorana Church (Box 8)
    - Palazzo Reale & Cappella Palatina (Box 8)
    - S. Cataldo (Box 8)
    - S. Giovanni Degli Eremiti (Box 8)
    - La Ziza (Box 8)
  - Parma (Box 8)
  - Pavia (Box 8)
    - Churches (Box 8)
      - S. Michele (Box 8)
        - Exterior (Box 8)
        - Interior (Box 8)
        - Sculpture (Box 8)
  - Perugia (Box 8)
  - Pienza (Box 8)
  - Pisa [Slide box 46] (Box 8)
    - Baptistry (Box 8)
    - Campanile (Box 8)
    - Cathedral (Box 8)
    - Cathedral Group (Box 8)
  - Pistoia (Box 8)
    - Cathedral (Box 8)
    - S. Giovanni Fourcivitas (Box 8)
  - Pomposa (Box 8)
  - Portonovo [Slide box 47] (Box 8)
  - Rivolta D'Adda (Box 8)
  - Ruvo (Box 8)
  - Sagra di San Michele (Box 8)
  - Siena (Box 8)
  - Siponto (Box 8)
  - Spoleto (Box 8)
  - Syracuse (Box 8)
  - Taranto (Box 8)
  - Trani (Box 8)
  - Troia (Box 8)
  - Tuscania (Box 8)
  - Verona (Box 8)
  - Volterra (Box 8)
- Norway (Box 8)
  - Gol (Box 8)
  - Hallingdal (Box 8)
  - Nybgaarden (Box 8)
  - Setesdal (Box 8)
  - Urnes (Box 8)
- Portugal (Box 8)
  - Various (Box 8)
- Russia (Box 8)
  - Kiev (Box 8)
  - Nereditsa (Box 8)
  - Novgorod [Slide boxes 47-48] (Box 8)
  - Pskov [Slide box 48] (Box 8)
  - Tiflis (Tbilisi) (Box 8)
  - Vladimir (Box 8)
- Spain (Box 8)
  - Aguero (Box 8)
  - Aran (Box 8)
  - Avila (Box 8)
    - Various (Box 8)
    - S. Vicente (Box 8)
  - Barcelona (Box 8)
  - Biota (Box 8)
  - Cardona (Box 8)
  - Egea de los Caballeros (Box 8)
  - El Frago (Box 8)
  - Fromista (Box 8)
  - Gerona (Box 8)
  - Huesca (Box 8)
  - Jaca [Slide box 49] (Box 9)
  - Leon (Box 9)
    - S. Isidro (Box 9)
  - Poblet (Box 9)
    - Abbey (Box 9)
      - Exterior (Box 9)
      - Interior (Box 9)
  - Ripoll (Box 9)
  - Salamanca (Box 9)
    - Cathedral (Old) (Box 9)
  - Sanguesa (Box 9)
  - S. Juan de la Peña (Box 9)
  - San Pere de Roda (Box 9)
  - Santiago de Compostela (Box 9)
    - Exterior (Box 9)
    - Portico de la Gloria (Box 9)
    - Portico de Platerias (Box 9)
    - Interior (Box 9)
  - Segovia (Box 9)
  - Silos (Box 9)
    - S. Domingo (Box 9)
  - Soria (Box 9)
  - Tahull (Box 9)
  - Uncastillo (Box 9)
- Switzerland (Box 9)
  [Slide box 50]
  - Geneva (Box 9)
  - Payerne (Box 9)
  - Romainmotier (Box 9)
  - St. Sulpice (Box 9)
- Yugoslavia (Box 9)
  - Decani (Box 9)
  - Durdevi Stubovi (Box 9)
  - Gracanica (Box 9)
  - Kalenic (Box 9)
  - Kursumlija (Box 9)
  - Lazarica (Box 9)
  - Ljubostinja (Box 9)
  - Naupara (Box 9)
  - Nerezi (Box 9)
  - Ohrid (Box 9)
  - Pec (Box 9)
  - Prilep (Box 9)
  - Ravanica (Box 9)
  - Resava (Box 9)
  - Sopocani (Box 9)
  - Staro Nagoricino (Box 9)
  - Studenica (Box 9)
  - Zagreb (Box 9)
- Gothic (Box 9)
  [Slide box 51]
  - Villard de Honnecourt (Box 9)
    - Miscellaneous Titles (Box 9)
    - Heads, figures, animals (Box 9)
  - General (Box 9)
    - Miscellaneous Titles (Box 9)
    - Construction (Box 9)
    - Flying Buttresses (Box 9)
    - Houses (Box 9)
    - Plans (Box 9)
    - Vaulting [Slide box 52] (Box 9)
  - Gothic Austria (Box 9)
    - Salzburg (Box 9)
      - Vienna (Box 9)
        - S. Stephen's Cathedral (Box 9)
  - Gothic Belgium (Box 9)
    - Antwerp (Box 9)
    - Bruges (Box 9)
    - Brussels (Box 9)
    - Ghent (Box 9)
    - Liege (Box 9)
    - Ypres (Box 9)
  - Gothic Britain (Box 9)
    - Barns (Box 9)
    - Fortifications (Box 9)
    - Houses (Box 9)
    - Arundel Castle, Sussex (Box 9)
    - Barton-on-Humber (Box 9)
    - Bath (Box 9)
    - Beverly [Slide box 53] (Box 9)
    - Beaumaris Castle (Box 9)
    - Blythburg (Box 9)
    - Bodiam Castle, Sussex (Box 9)
    - Boston (Box 9)
    - Brinkburn Priory (Box 9)
    - Bristol (Box 9)
    - Caerphilly (Box 9)
    - Cambridge (Box 9)
    - Canterbury (Box 9)
      - Cathedral (Box 9)
        - Exterior (Box 9)
        - Interior (Box 9)
          - Choir [Slide box 54] (Box 9)
          - S. Anselm's Chapel (Box 9)
          - Trinity Chapel (Box 9)
          - Crypt (Box 9)
          - Cloisters (Box 9)
          - Infirmary (Box 9)
          - Treasury (Box 9)
          - Water Tower (Box 9)
    - Carnarvon, Wales (Box 9)
    - Castleacre Priory, Norfolk (Box 9)
    - Chester (Box 9)
    - Chichester [Slide box 55] (Box 10)
    - Chipping Camden (Box 10)
    - Cirencester (Box 10)
    - Cleeve (Box 10)
    - Cobham (Box 10)
    - Conway (Wales) (Box 10)
    - Dunfermline, Scotland (Box 10)
    - Ely (Box 10)
      - Cathedral (Box 10)
        - Exterior (Box 10)
        - Interior (Box 10)
          - Lady Chapel (Box 10)
    - Exeter [Slide boxes 55-56] (Box 10)
    - Flint (Wales) [Slide box 56] (Box 10)
    - Fotheringay (Box 10)
    - Fountains Abbey (Box 10)
    - Glastonbury (Box 10)
    - Gloucester (Box 10)
    - Haddon Hall (Box 10)
    - Harlech (Wales) (Box 10)
    - Hampton Court (Box 10)
    - Hereford (Box 10)
    - Higham Ferrars (Box 10)
    - Howden (Box 10)
    - Kenilworth (Box 10)
    - Lincoln (Box 10)
      - Cathedral (Box 10)
        - Exterior [Slide boxes 56-57] (Box 10)
        - Interior [Slide box 57] (Box 10)
          - Angel Choir (Box 10)
    - Litchfield (Box 10)
    - Little Moreton Hall (Box 10)
    - London (Box 10)
      - Churches (Box 10)
        - Old S. Paul's (Box 10)
        - Westminster Abbey (Box 10)
          - Exterior (Box 10)
          - Interior [Slide box 58] (Box 10)
            - Chapter House (Box 10)
            - Henry VII Chapel (Box 10)
      - Government buildings (Box 10)
      - Palaces (Box 10)
    - Lower Brockhampton (Box 10)
    - Norwich (Box 10)
    - Oxford (Box 10)
      - University (Box 10)
        - Christ Church College (Box 10)
        - Magdalene College (Box 10)
        - Merton College (Box 10)
        - New College (Box 10)
    - Peterborough (Box 10)
    - Richmond, Yorkshire (Box 10)
    - Rievaulx (Box 10)
    - Ripon [Slide box 59] (Box 10)
    - Rochester (Box 10)
    - Salisbury (Box 10)
      - Cathedral (Box 10)
        - Exterior (Box 10)
        - Interior (Box 10)
          - Chapel House [Slide box 59-60] (Box 10)
          - Cloister [Slide box 60] (Box 10)
    - Sherborne (Box 10)
    - Shrewsbury, Salop (Box 10)
    - Southwell (Box 10)
    - Stokesay Castle (Box 10)
    - Stratford-on-Avon (Box 10)
    - Thetford Priory (Box 10)
    - Tintern Abbey (Box 10)
    - Warwick (Box 10)
    - Wells (Box 10)
      - Cathedral (Box 10)
        - Exterior (Box 10)
          - Exterior Sculpture (Box 10)
        - Interior (Box 10)
          - Interior Sculpture [Slide box 61] (Box 11)
          - Bishop's Palace, Barn (Box 11)
          - Chapter House (Box 11)
    - Winchester (Box 11)
    - Windsor (Box 11)
    - Worcester (Box 11)
    - Wrexham (Box 11)
    - York (Box 11)
      - Churches (Box 11)
        - Cathedral (Minster) (Box 11)
          - Exterior (Box 11)
          - Interior (Box 11)
            - Chapter House (Box 11)
  - Gothic Cyprus (Box 11)
    - Bellapais Abbey (Box 11)
      - Famagusta (Box 11)
      - Kolossi (Box 11)
      - Nicosia (Box 11)
  - Gothic Czechoslovakia (Box 11)
    - Miscellaneous Titles & Cities [Slide boxes 61-62] (Box 11)
  - Gothic France (Box 11)
    [Slide box 62]
    - General (Box 11)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 11)
        - Castles (Box 11)
        - Houses (Box 11)
    - Known sites (Box 11)
      - Aigues-Mortes (Box 11)
      - Albi (Box 11)
        - Cathedral (Box 11)
          - Exterior (Box 11)
          - Interior (Box 11)
      - Ambierle (Box 11)
      - Amboise (Box 11)
      - Amiens (Box 11)
        - Cathedral (Box 11)
          - Air views (Box 11)
          - Exterior (Box 11)
          - Interior [Slide box 63] (Box 11)
            - Various (Box 11)
            - Crossing (Box 11)
          - Exterior Sculpture (Box 11)
            - Miscellaneous (Box 11)
            - West Façade Sculpture (Box 11)
              - Center door (Beau Dieu) (Box 11)
              - Left door (North), Confessor or St. Fermin (Box 11)
              - Right door (South), Mother of God (Box 11)
              - Dado (Box 11)
            - South Transept Façade (Box 11)
          - Interior Sculpture (Box 11)
            - Church of S. Remy (Box 11)
      - Angers (Box 11)
        - Cathedral [Slide box 64] (Box 11)
      - Auch (Box 11)
      - Auxerre (Box 11)
      - Avignon (Box 11)
      - Bayeux (Box 11)
      - Beaune (Box 11)
      - Beauvais (Box 11)
        - T. Etienne (Box 11)
        - Cathedral (Box 11)
      - Blois (Box 11)
      - Bordeaux (Box 11)
      - Bourg (Box 11)
      - Bourges (Box 11)
        - Cathedral (S. Etienne) (Box 11)
          - Plans and Sections (Box 11)
          - Exterior [Slide box 65] (Box 11)
          - Interior (Box 11)
          - Exterior Sculpture (Box 11)
            - West Façade Sculpture (Box 11)
        - Houses (Box 11)
        - Caen (Box 11)
        - Cambrai (Box 11)
        - Carcassonne (Box 11)
      - Celles-Sur-Belle (Box 11)
      - Chaalis (Box 11)
      - Chaise-Dieu (Box 11)
      - Chalons-Sur-Marne [Slide boxes 65-66] (Box 11)
      - Chalon sur Saone [Slide box 66] (Box 11)
      - Chartres (Box 11)
        - Cathedral (Box 11)
          - Plans & Sections (Box 11)
          - Air Views & Distant Views (Box 11)
          - Exterior (Box 11)
            - West Façade (Box 11)
            - Towers (Box 11)
            - North Side (Box 11)
            - South Side (Box 11)
            - Buttresses [Slide boxes 66-67] (Box 11)
              - Interior [Slide box 67] (Box 12)
              - Exterior Sculpture (Box 12)
                - West Façade Sculpture (Box 12)
                - Center Door (Box 12)
                - Left Door (North) [Slide boxes 67-68] (Box 12)
                - Right Door (South) [Slide box 68] (Box 12)
                - North Porch Sculpture (Box 12)
                - Center Door (Box 12)
                - Left Door (East) (Box 12)
                - Right Door (West) (Box 12)
                - South Porch Sculpture (Box 12)
                - Center Door (West) [Slide boxes 68-69] (Box 12)
                - Left Door (West) [Slide box 69] (Box 12)
                - Right Door (East) (Box 12)
              - Interior Sculpture (Box 12)
                - Choir Screen (Box 12)
        - Houses (Box 12)
      - Chateaudun (Box 12)
      - Chaumont (Box 12)
      - Chinon (Box 12)
      - Clermont-Ferrand (Box 12)
      - Cluny (Box 12)
      - Coucy (Box 12)
      - Coutances [Slide box 70] (Box 12)
      - Dijon (Box 12)
      - Etampes (Box 12)
      - Etretat (Box 12)
      - Evreux (Box 12)
      - Flavigny (Box 12)
      - Fontenay (Box 12)
      - Fontfroide (Box 12)
      - Frejus (Box 12)
      - La Ferte (Box 12)
      - Langeais (Box 12)
      - Langres (Box 12)
      - Laon (Box 12)
        - Cathedral (Box 12)
          - Exterior (Box 12)
          - Interior (Box 12)
          - Sculpture (Box 12)
      - Le Barraux [Slide box 71] (Box 12)
      - Le Mans (Box 12)
      - Cathedral S. Julien (Box 12)
      - Les Andelys (Box 12)
      - Limoges (Box 12)
      - Lisieux (Box 12)
      - Loches (Box 12)
      - Louviers (Box 12)
      - Lyons (Box 12)
      - Mantes (Box 12)
        - Notre Dame (Box 12)
      - Mereville (Box 12)
      - Metz (Box 12)
      - Mirande (Box 12)
      - Monpazier (Box 12)
      - Mont S. Michelle (Box 12)
        - Abbey (Box 12)
          - Various (Box 12)
          - General Views (Box 12)
          - Main Church Exterior (Box 12)
          - Main Church Interior (Box 12)
      - Moulins (Box 12)
      - Nantes (Box 12)
      - Narbonne (Box 12)
      - Nevers [Slide box 72] (Box 12)
      - Noyon (Box 12)
        - Cathedral (Box 12)
          - Exterior (Box 12)
          - Interior (Box 12)
      - Nyons (Box 12)
      - Paris (Box 12)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 12)
        - Churches (Box 12)
          - Church of the Celestins (Box 12)
          - Notre Dame (Box 12)
            - Plans & Sections (Box 12)
            - Air Views (Box 12)
            - Exterior (Box 12)
              - Exterior South (River) Side (Box 12)
              - Exterior Transepts (Box 12)
              - West Facade [Slide boxes 72-73] (Box 12–13)
              - Apse (Box 13)
            - Exterior details (Box 13)
              - Miscellaneous (Box 13)
              - Flying Buttresses (Box 13)
              - Roofs & Pinnacles (Box 13)
              - Rose Windows (Box 13)
            - Interior (Box 13)
            - Exterior Sculpture (Box 13)
              - Gargoyles & Chimeras (Box 13)
              - Fragments (Box 13)
              - West Façade (Box 13)
                - Center door (Box 13)
                - Left (North) door (Box 13)
                - Right (South) door (Box 13)
              - North Side (Box 13)
              - South Transept door (Portal of S. Etienne) (Box 13)
                - South Side Dado (Box 13)
          - S. Chapelle [Slide box 74] (Box 13)
            - Various (Box 13)
            - Exterior (Box 13)
            - Interior (Box 13)
          - S. Genevieve (Box 13)
          - S. Germain Des Pres (Box 13)
          - S. Germain L'Auxerrois (Box 13)
          - S. Martin Des Champs (Box 13)
          - S. Pierre de Montmartre (Box 13)
          - S. Severin (Box 13)
        - Government Buildings (Box 13)
        - Houses & Hotels (Box 13)
          - Hotel De Cluny (Box 13)
          - Hotel De Sens (Box 13)
        - Palaces (Box 13)
        - Prisons (Box 13)
        - Towers (Box 13)
      - PierreFonds (Box 13)
      - Poitiers (Box 13)
      - Provins (Box 13)
      - Rampillon (Box 13)
      - Reims [Slide box 75] (Box 13)
        - Cathedral (Box 13)
          - Plans & Sections (Box 13)
            - Exterior (Box 13)
              - West Façade (Box 13)
              - North Transept (Box 13)
              - South Side (Box 13)
              - Apse (Chevet) (Box 13)
              - During Cleaning (Box 13)
            - Interior (Box 13)
            - Exterior Sculpture (Box 13)
              - West Façade (Box 13)
                - Center door (Box 13)
                - Left Jamb (Presentation) (Box 13)
                - Right Jamb (South, Visitation & Annunciation) [Slide box 76] (Box 13)
                - Left door (North) (Box 13)
                - Right door (South) (Box 13)
              - North Transept (Box 13)
                - Center Door (Box 13)
                - Left Door (Box 13)
                - Right Door (Box 13)
              - South Transept (Box 13)
            - Interior Sculpture (Box 13)
              - Capitals (Box 13)
              - West Walls (Box 13)
              - S. Nicase (Box 13)
              - S. Remi (Box 13)
      - Rouen (Box 13)
        - Cathedral (Box 13)
          - Exterior (Box 13)
          - Interior [Slide box 77] (Box 13)
          - Sculpture (Box 13)
      - S. Maclou (Box 13)
      - S. Ouen (Box 13)
      - S. Denis (Box 13)
        - Plans (Box 13)
        - Sections (Box 13)
        - Models (Box 13)
        - Exterior (Box 13)
          - Façade [Slide boxes 77-78] (Box 13)
          - Apse or Chevet [Slide box 78] (Box 13)
        - Interior (Box 13)
          - Various (Box 13)
          - Ambulatory (Box 13)
          - Narthex (Box 13)
          - Nave (Box 13)
          - Choir (Box 13)
          - Crypt (Box 13)
        - Sculpture (Box 13)
          - Capitals (Box 13)
          - Fragments (Box 13)
          - West Façade [Slide box 79] (Box 14)
          - South Transept (Box 14)
      - S. Germer-de-Fly (Box 14)
      - S. Leu D'Esserten (Box 14)
      - S. Loup-De-Naud (Box 14)
      - S. Martin-aux-Bois (Box 14)
      - S. Pierre-Sur-Dives (Box 14)
      - St. Pol De Leon (Box 14)
      - S. Quentin (Box 14)
      - S. Riquier (Box 14)
      - S. Thibault-en-Auxois (Box 14)
      - Sees (Box 14)
      - Senanque (Box 14)
      - Senlis (Box 14)
        - Cathedral of Notre Dame (Box 14)
          - Exterior & Interior (Box 14)
          - Sculpture (Box 14)
      - Sens (Box 14)
        - Cathedral (Box 14)
          - Exterior (Box 14)
          - Interior (Box 14)
      - Soissons [Slide boxes 79-80] (Box 14)
      - Strassbourg [Slide box 80] (Box 14)
        - Various (Box 14)
        - Cathedral (Box 14)
          - Exterior (Box 14)
          - Interior (Box 14)
            - Sculpture details (Box 14)
      - Sully (Box 14)
      - Toulouse (Box 14)
        - Churches (Box 14)
          - Church of the Jacobins (Box 14)
          - S. Etienne (Box 14)
      - Tours (Box 14)
      - Troyes (Box 14)
        - Cathedral (Box 14)
      - Vendome (Box 14)
      - Verdun (Box 14)
      - Vezelay (Box 14)
        - La Madeleine (Box 14)
      - Vincennes (Box 14)
  - Gothic Germany (Box 14)
    [Slide box 81]
    - Aachen (Box 14)
    - Augsburg (Box 14)
    - Bacharach (Box 14)
    - Bad Doberan (Box 14)
    - Bamberg (Box 14)
      - Cathedral (Box 14)
        - Exterior (Box 14)
        - Interior (Box 14)
    - Bebenhausen (Box 14)
    - Bergen auf Rugen (Box 14)
    - Braunschweig (Box 14)
    - Cologne [Slide boxes 81-82] (Box 14)
    - Constance [Slide box 82] (Box 14)
    - Dinkelsbuhl (Box 14)
    - Erfurt (Box 14)
    - Freiburg im Breisgau (Box 14)
    - Gmund (Box 14)
    - Ingoldstadt (Box 14)
    - Keitum on Sylt Island (Box 14)
    - Landshut (Box 14)
    - Limburg an der Lahn (Box 14)
    - Lubeck [Slide box 83] (Box 14)
    - Luneburg (Box 14)
    - Magdeburg (Box 14)
    - Marienburg (Box 14)
    - Maulbronn (Box 14)
    - Munich (Box 14)
    - Naumburg (Box 14)
    - Neubrandenburg (Box 14)
    - Neuss (Box 14)
    - Nordlingen (Box 14)
    - Nuremburg (Box 14)
      - Castles (Box 14)
      - Churches [Slide box 84] (Box 14)
        - Frauenkirche (Box 14)
        - S. Lorenz (Box 14)
        - S. Sebaldus (Box 14)
      - Squares (Box 14)
    - Oppenheim (Box 14)
    - Pirna (Box 14)
    - Prenzlau (Box 14)
    - Regensburg (Box 14)
    - Rothenburg (Box 14)
    - Stralsund (Box 14)
    - Trier (Box 14)
    - Ulm (Box 14)
    - Wismar (Box 14)
    - Wolgast (Box 14)
  - Gothic Holland (Box 15)
    [Slide box 85]
    - Various (Box 15)
  - Gothic Hungary (Box 15)
    - Various (Box 15)
  - Gothic Italy (Box 15)
    - Aquila (Box 15)
    - Arezzo (Box 15)
    - Assisi (Box 15)
      - Churches (Box 15)
        - S. Francesco (Box 15)
          - Upper Church (Box 15)
          - Lower Church (Box 15)
    - Bagnoregio (Box 15)
    - Bologna (Box 15)
    - Capistrello [Slide box 86] (Box 15)